placeoforigin.in 2017-02-18

# privacy-policy

### PRIVACY POLICY

Craftsvilla Handicrafts Pvt Limited is the operator and licensee of www.craftsvilla.com (“ **Website** ”) and www.placeoforigin.in Craftsvilla can be contacted by e-mail at customercare@craftsvilla.com .  The protection and security of your personal information is one of Craftsvilla’s top priorities. This online Privacy Policy discloses Craftsvilla’s information practices for this Website and subscriber / membership based services (“ **Services** ”) including the type of information being collected, method of such information collection, use of such information and sharing of such information with third parties.  

By using this Website you agree to accept the terms of this Privacy Policy as well as the Website’s Terms of Use.  By accessing or using this Website you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in any manner described in this Privacy Policy.  This Privacy Policy extends to both, users who visit the Website but do not transact business on the Website (“ **Users** ”) as well as users who are registered and are authorized by the Website to transact business on the Website (“ **Members** ”).

“ **Personal Information** ” refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact or locate the person, to whom such information pertains including, but not limited to, name, address, phone number, fax number, email address, financial profiles, identification  number and credit card information. 

PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING TERMS OF OUR PRIVACY POLICY

**PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT MAY BE COLLECTED**

Craftsvilla and/or PlaceofOrigin.in shall collect and store any information that you may provide on our Websites.  To enable you to become a member or subscriber of our Websites we need to have your basic Personal Information.  Apart from this, when you visit our site, our systems collect details about your computer’s personal information like your IP address.  Please note that your IP address does not identify you personally.  
No use or Services available on this Website are directed towards children.  Craftsvilla and/or PlaceofOrigin.in does not knowingly collect Personal Information from children or sell of its products to children.

**USE OF INFORMATION COLLECTED  **

The Company owns all the information collected via the Website.  As applicable, the information collected by the Comapny shall be used to contact you about the Websites and Website related news and Services available on the Websites; monitor and improve the Website; calculate the number of visitors to the Website and to know the geographical locations of the visitors; update you on all the special offers available on the Website and provide you with a better shopping experience.  

Please note that when you place an order, some of your Personal Information will be passed on to the others who shall need to have access to some Personal Information like courier companies, credit card processing companies, vendors etc. to enable them and Craftsvilla and/or PlaceofOrigin.in perform their duties and fulfill your order requirements.  

The Company does not allow any unauthorized persons or organization to use any information that Craftsvilla and/or PlaceofOrigin.in may collect from you through these Websites.  
In the event the Company is required to respond to subpoenas, court orders or other legal process, your Personal Information may be disclosed pursuant to such subpoenas, court order or legal process, which may be without notice to you.  

Cookies are small pieces of information saved by your browser onto your computer.  Cookies are used to record various aspects of your visit and assist Craftsvilla to provide you with uninterrupted service. Craftsvilla and/or PlaceofOrigin.in do not use cookies to save Personal Information for outside uses.

As you browse www.craftsvilla.com and/or PlaceofOrigin.in, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our display advertising partner, AdRoll (http://www.adroll.com), then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with www.craftsvilla.com. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number. You can visit this page http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/ to opt out of AdRoll and their partners’ targeted advertising. 

The Company may share collective information such as demographics and Website usage statistics with our sponsors, advertisers or other third parties (such third parties do not include the Company`s marketing partners and network providers).  When this type of information is shared, such parties do not have access to your Personal Information.

This Website may contain links which may lead you to other Websites.  Please note that once you leave our Website you will be subjected to the Privacy Policy of the other website and this Privacy Policy will no longer apply.

BY USING THIS WEBSITE, YOU SIGNIFY YOUR AGREEMENT TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, THE COMPANY RESERVES THE RIGHT, IN OUR SOLE DISCRETION, TO CHANGE, MODIFY, ADD OR DELETE PORTIONS OF THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AT ANY TIME.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to through our Website or write to us at customercare@craftsvilla.com .

#### OUR POLICY

We firmly believe in helping our customers as far as possible, and therefore have a liberal customer policy.

#### RESOLUTION OF CONCERNS

Please email any concern to  [support@placeoforigin.in](mailto:support@placeoforigin.in). 

If the concern is regarding the taste/quality/ingredients of the food product, we will refer the issue to the concerned producer and make suitable efforts to help resolve the complaint.

If you think you have received the food items in an unsatisfactory condition or if the packaging is tampered with or damaged before delivery, please email us at [support@placeoforigin.in](mailto:support@placeoforigin.in) with your Order Number & relevant photographic evidence within 24 hours of the package being delivered to you/your address. We will share the pictures of the shipment and individual pictures of the boxes with the Food Vendors and the courier partner for resolution. If the claim is genuine as found by us, the Food Vendor and the Courier Partner, we will issue a coupon code for the amount pertaining to the unsatisfactory shipment. You can utilise the coupon code for subsequent purchases on the website. The coupon code cannot be encashed or refunded. 

If unfortunately you have to cancel an order, please contact our customer care at +91 8039 591 648 or email us at support@placeoforigin.in If you cancel your order before your food items have been shipped, we will refund the entire amount. However, once the order has been shipped (that is, it has been produced by the vendor and handed over to the delivery agent), we will not be in a position to address any cancellation requests. You will be appreciate that these are speciality food products and the loss of shelf life/transit damage will render them unsuitable for reuse/resale and hence we cannot accept cancellation or return of shipments. Only in case of valid cancellation requests, the refund for the same will be made in the same method that the payment is received, within 10 working days from the date of cancellation of order.

If we suspect any fraudulent transaction by any customer or any transaction which defies the terms & conditions of using the website, we at our sole discretion could cancel such orders. We will maintain a negative list of all fraudulent transactions and customers and would deny access to them or cancel any orders placed by them.

#### SHIPPING & DELIVERY POLICY

Placeoforigin is committed to deliver your order with good quality packaging within given time frame.

To ensure that your order reaches you in good condition, in the shortest span of time, we ship through reputed courier agencies only and to the specific geographies serviced by them. . We ship throughout the week during normal working hours except Saturday/Sunday/Public holidays (which are excluded to prevent the lag in shipments).

We currently do not levy any service charge.

Orders are dispatched within 1-2 working days post the receipt of the order and depending on availability of the fresh product. Delivery of all orders will be duly done to the address as mentioned by you at the time of placing the order. In order to avoid disappointment, we will not accept orders that need to be delivered to any pincode not serviced by our reputed courier partners.

Please note that the delivery timing depends on a number of factors like: weather, unforeseen events, traffic conditions and other special events. However, we will always endeavour to complete the delivery as early as possible and keep you updated in case of any changes. We are not responsible for any delay caused by any unforeseen time lags by the courier companies in delivering the parcels to the customer, or if the customer is not available at the time of delivery.
